When in doubt, don't.
That's the best advice I can give to you when you're asking yourself, "how do I decide on whether or not to go on a third date with this person".
This is Dr. Paul, author of Boomer Girls, a boomer women's guide to men and dating.
Let me let you know this.
If you have to ask yourself a question, the answer is probably no, so don't go there.
There has to be a reason for you to sit back, if it happens to be, that gut feeling, you have that sixth sense, listen to it.
Don't say it's okay, I don't have anything better to do because you're only going to go from bad to worse and the key to that is you.
You have to be happy with you. Yourself image has to be such that you respect you and you look at yourself in the morning and you see yourself in that mirror and you say, "did I do the right thing?".
The answer better be yes because you love yourself a lot more.
By the way, you know, having people like you is being popular.
You, liking yourself is being happy.
This is Dr. Paul.
May your fantasies of the day, be your realities of tomorrow.